

CONTACT

- Bogura, Bangladesh
- abidshahriar7@gmail.com
- +8801726389558
- https://github.com/abid-shahriar
- https://linkedin.com/in/abidshahriar
- https://abidshahriar.me

SKILLS

- HTML | CSS | SCSS
- JavaScript | TypeScript
- ReactJS | NextJS
- Redux | ContextApi
- NodeJS | Express
- Mongoose | MongoDB
- Postgres | Prisma | Knex
- Git | Github

LANGUAGES

- Bengali
- English
- Hindi

HOBBIES

- Coding
- Travelling
- Cooking

ABID SHAHRIAR

Full Stack JavaScript Dev.

SUMMARY

Creative full stack JavaScript Developer with 2.5+ years of experience and have a passion for building responsive, interactive and secure web applications. I have a strong background in web development and have worked on a wide range of projects. I like learning new stacks and always try to keep myself updated with the latest technologies.

EDUCATION

Bogura Zilla School

Secondary School Certificate in Science

Feb 2008 - Feb 2016

Govt. Azizul Haque College, Bogura

Higher Secondary Certificate in Science

Feb 2016 - Feb 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Feb 2019 - Oct 2020

I stared freelancing with some local clients of my area. I built school/restaurant and small e-commerce websites for them. After that I started freelancing with some remote clients. I gained a bunch of new skills doing this.

Frontend Engineer

Wikiance | Nov 2020 - Sep 2021

I mostly worked on their flagship product called Techiio. I was the lead developer on the project. My responsibility was implementing api by coordinating with backend developers, adding new features, testing, scaling up, bug fixing, training interns etc. Learned a lot about teamwork, communication, best practices, and how to work in a fast-paced environment from here.

Backend Engineer

ValkyrieTM | Nov 2021 - Present

It's a SASS based Company so I get to work on different kinds of projects and learn new technologies. My responsibility here is creating secure and scalable backend, doing research and communicating with the frontend devs to make an app alive.